ILGWU Association Agreements, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/145
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1956 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New England Clothing and Rainwear Manufacturers Assoc. (Boston), 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1947 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Amended 6/47
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1947 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Amended 2/47
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1947 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Extension 12/47
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Extension 12/49
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1952 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Amended 10/52
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1958 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Employers Association (Fall River), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Twin Cities Dress Manufacturers Association (Minneapolis), 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Minnesota Apparel Industries (Minneapolis), 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Minnesota Apparel Industries (Minneapolis), 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1938-1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1946-1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Amended 1/68
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Amended 2/69
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Amended 7/68
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Coat and Suit Branch), 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Dress
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1951-1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Sportswear
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Dress and sportswear
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Amended 8/68
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (Dress and Sportswear Branch), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Assoc. (shipping and receiving), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1944 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1946-1951 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Amended 11/66
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  master
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Amended 2/71
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Dress supplement
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Amended 10/67
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (dress branch), 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1921 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1946-1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1957-1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Amended 2/46
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Amended 2/45
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (cloak and suit group), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (sportswear and cotton Garment division), 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (sportswear and cotton Garment division), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (sportswear and cotton Garment division), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (sportswear and cotton Garment division), 1944-1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (sportswear and cotton Garment division), 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (sportswear and cotton Garment division), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (sportswear and cotton Garment division), 1946-1951 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1946-1951 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1954 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (underwear group), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1944-1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1946-1951 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (embroidery group), 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Amended 7/1/68
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Amended 7/17/68
- Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis (curtain division), 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Amended 1/67
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Amended 7/67
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Associated Garment Industries of St Louis (plastics division), 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- New Jersey Double Knit Association, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Double Knit Association, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Double Knit Association, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Double Knit Association, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Double Knit Association, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Knitwear Association, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- New Jersey Knitwear Association, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Knit Manufacturers of New Jersey, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Knit Manufacturers of New Jersey, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Knit Manufacturers of New Jersey, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Knit Manufacturers of New Jersey, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Knit Manufacturers of New Jersey, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Knit Manufacturers of New Jersey, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Knit Manufacturers of New Jersey, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1949-1952 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1949-1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers (NY-out-of-town agreement applicable in New Jersey), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Washable Dress Contractors Association, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Cleveland Dress Manufacturers Association, 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Cleveland Knitgoods Industry (Standard independent), 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cleveland Knitgoods Industry (Standard independent), 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cleveland Knitgoods Industry (Standard independent), 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cleveland Knitgoods Industry (Standard independent), 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cleveland Knitgoods Industry (Standard independent), 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cleveland Garment Manufacturers Association, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Referee's Decision
- Cleveland Garment Manufacturers Association, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cleveland Garment Manufacturers Association, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cleveland Garment Manufacturers Association, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cleveland Garment Manufacturers Association, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cleveland Garment Manufacturers Association, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers Association, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Ohio Apparel Manufacturers Association, 1935-1941 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers Association, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers Association, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers Association, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers Association, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers Association, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Women's Garment Manufacturers Association of Philadelphia, 1925-1926 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Women's Garment Manufacturers Association of Philadelphia, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Women's Garment Manufacturers Association of Philadelphia, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Women's Garment Manufacturers Association of Philadelphia, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Cleveland Apparel Manufacturers Association, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Philadelphia Ladies' Garment Association, 1925-1927 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Ladies' Garment Association, 1923-1924 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1945-1948 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1935-1938 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Portland, OR, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Blouse and Dress Contractors Association, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Blouse and Dress Contractors Association, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 18)